Guide to the Reuben A. Holden, Secretary of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Secretary: General Correspondence and Subject File, 1901-1972 1953-1971; Series II
  - Music School
    - 1959-1968 (Box 114, Folder 994-997)
    - 1967-1971 (Box 114, Folder 998-1000)
  - Musical Instruments: Steinert Collection, 1913 (Box 114, Folder 1000A)
  - N-general, 1958-1971 (Box 114, Folder 1001-1005)
  - National service, 1966-1967 (Box 114, Folder 1006)
  - Naval Science, 1954-1968 (Box 115, Folder 1007-1015)
  - Negroes, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 1015A)
  - New Haven, City of, 1953-1969 (Box 116, Folder 1016-1020)
  - New Haven city plan, 1938-1955 (Box 117, Folder 1020A)
  - New Haven College, 1953-1960 (Box 117, Folder 1021-1022)
  - New Haven Foundation, 1962-1969 (Box 117, Folder 1023)
  - New Haven Symphony, 1968-1969 (Box 117, Folder 1024)
  - New Journal, The, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 1025)
  - Newcomers Club, 1959-1968 (Box 117, Folder 1026)
  - Nobel Prize to Yale men, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 1027)
  - Northeastern Institute, 1953-1959 (Box 117, Folder 1028)
  - Nuclear Center for Connecticut, 1961-1966 (Box 117, Folder 1029)
  - Nuclear Structure Department, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 1029A)
  - Nursing School, 1955-1969 (Box 117, Folder 1030-1031)
  - O-general, 1963-1971 (Box 117, Folder 1032-1033)
  - Oldest living graduate, 1945-1967 (Box 117, Folder 1033A)
  - O'Hearn, Frank, undated (Box 117, Folder 1034)
  - Organ, Newberry Memorial, 1917 (Box 117, Folder 1034A)
  - P-general, 1957-1971 (Box 118, Folder 1035-1039)
  - Pageant: Yale, 1916 (Box 118, Folder 1039A)
  - Parents' Committee, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 1040)
  - Parents' Day
    - 1958-1968 (Box 118, Folder 1041-1043)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 119, Folder 1044)
  - Parents and alumni: information packet, 1970 (Box 119, Folder 1045)
  - Parking Authority, 1968-1969 (Box 119, Folder 1046)
  - Patents, 1933-1950 (Box 119, Folder 1046A)
  - Payroll, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 1047)
  - Peabody Museum
    - 1953-1968 (Box 119, Folder 1048-1052)
    - 1970 (Box 119, Folder 1053)
  - Peace Corps, 1961-1967 (Box 119, Folder 1054-1055)
  - Personnel Office
    - 1954-1963 (Box 119, Folder 1056)
    - 1963-1971 (Box 120, Folder 1057-1059)
  - Phi Beta Kappa
    - 1958-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1060)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 120, Folder 1061)
    - Dinner, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 1062-1063)
    - 1969 (Box 120, Folder 1064)
    - Dinner, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 1065)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 120, Folder 1066)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1067)
    - Dinner, 1970-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1068)
  - Philosophy Department, 1957-1969 (Box 121, Folder 1069-1071)
  - Philosophy Library, 1970 (Box 121, Folder 1072)
  - Physics Department, 1953-1963,1966-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1073-1074)
  - Pierson Chair, Pierson and Woolsey Statues: Suggested relocation of, 1931 (Box 121, Folder 1074A)
  - Placement Office, 1954-1967 (Box 121, Folder 1075-1076)
  - Plimpton letter, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 1077)
  - Police, Campus, 1965-1970 (Box 122, Folder 1078)
  - Political Science Department, 1954-1971 (Box 122, Folder 1079-1081)
  - Political Union, 1963-1965,1967-1971 (Box 122, Folder 1082-1083)
  - Portraits, University: correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 122, Folder 1084)
  - Poster locations, undated (Box 122, Folder 1085)
  - Prairie View Agricultural and Mechanical College, 1967-1968 (Box 122, Folder 1086)
  - President's Office
    - 1953-1970 (Box 122, Folder 1087)
    - 1953-1963 (Box 122, Folder 1088)
    - 1964-1971 (Box 123, Folder 1089-1093)
  - President's report, 1953-1958 (Box 123, Folder 1094)
  - Princeton University, 1953-1966 (Box 123, Folder 1095)
  - Prizes, 1968-1971 (Box 123, Folder 1096-1097)
  - Professorships, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1098)
  - Professorships,endowed, 1959-1963 (Box 123, Folder 1099)
  - Professional and Learned Societies, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 1100)
  - Programs, Summer (Box 124, Folder 1101)
    See: box 135, folder 1209-1210
  - Prom, 1967-1970 (Box 124, Folder 1102)
  - Provost's Office, 1953-1971 (Box 124, Folder 1103-1105)
  - Psychology Department, 1963-1968 (Box 124, Folder 1106)
  - Pursuivant of Arms, 1963-1967 (Box 124, Folder 1107)
  - Q-general, 1963-1969 (Box 124, Folder 1108)
  - R-general
    - 1953-1959 (Box 124, Folder 1108A)
    - 1956-1971 (Box 124, Folder 1109-1113)
  - Radio and television, 1954-1963 (Box 125, Folder 1114-1116)
  - Recommendation, Letters of, 1953-1968 (Box 125, Folder 1117-1121)
  - Recruiting material, 1964-1965 (Box 126, Folder 1122)
  - Red Cross, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 1123)
  - Registration, 1946-1966 (Box 126, Folder 1123A)
  - Relations with other countries, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 1124)
  - Religion Department, 1959-1968 (Box 126, Folder 1125-1126)
  - Religious ministry at Yale, 1957-1971 (Box 126, Folder 1127)
  - Remittance slips, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 1128)
  - Reports
    - Budget: general information, 1960-1968 (Box 126, Folder 1129)
    - "Colleges Are Too Cheap" by Herbert Solow in Fortune, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 1130)
    - Consultations re: university policies and administration of faculty, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 1131)
    - Course of Study Committee to General Faculty of Yale College, 1955 (Box 126, Folder 1132)
    - Forms: withdrawal from class for service: financial needs during decade, 1957-1967, n.d (Box 126, Folder 1133)
    - Griswold letter to Arthur S. Fleming re: National Defense Education Act Loyalty Oath, 1958 (Box 127, Folder 1134)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 1135-1136)
    - New Dimensions: Appeal of 1934 24th Reunion Gift Committee (J. Stephen Knight), 1934-1959 (Box 127, Folder 1137)
    - New Haven Conference on the Program for the Arts and Sciences, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 1138)
    - News Bureau: news release WTIC, 1963-1964 (Box 127, Folder 1139)
    - President's Committee on General Education, 1953 (Box 127, Folder 1140)
    - President's Committee on Nursing at Yale, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 1141)
    - "Program for the Arts and Sciences, Why Additional Capital is Needed for Yale College and Graduate School,", 1960 (Box 128, Folder 1142)
    - Remarks by Lloyd G. Reynolds at Alumni Board meeting, 1958 (Box 128, Folder 1143)
    - Treasurer's Office "Chart of Accounts,", 1953 (Box 128, Folder 1144)
    - "Why Yale?" by Alexander P.D. Maurelatos, Yale '58, from Yale Undergraduate, 1959 (Box 128, Folder 1145)
    - "Yale-New Haven Medical Center" by George S. Stevenson in Connecticut Medicine, 1959 (Box 128, Folder 1146)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1949-1962 (Box 128, Folder 1147-1148)
  - Retirement allowances, 1969 (Box 128, Folder 1149)
  - Retirement: letters and policies, 1970 (Box 128, Folder 1150)
  - Reunion, 1968-1971 (Box 128, Folder 1151)
  - Rhodes Scholarships, 1904-1967 (Box 128, Folder 1151A)
  - Riot, snowball, 1959 (Box 129, Folder 1152)
  - Rossiter's painting: The Founding of New Haven, 1944-1946 (Box 129, Folder 1152A)
  - Russian Chorus, 1959-1963 (Box 129, Folder 1154)
  - Russian Conference Exchange, Inter-University Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 129, Folder 1155)
  - Russian and Last European Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 129, Folder 1156)
  - Russian Foreign Policy, Conference on, 1961 (Box 129, Folder 1157)
  - S-general
    - 1953-1959 (Box 129, Folder 1157A)
    - 1957-1971 (Box 130, Folder 1158-1162)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 131, Folder 1163)
  - Saint Elmo Committee on Foreign Students, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 1164)
  - Schedules Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 131, Folder 1164A)
  - "Science and Society: A Forum for Discussion,", 1969 (Box 131, Folder 1166)
  - Secretary's Office
    - 1949-1961 (Box 131, Folder 1167)
    - 1963-1970 (Box 131, Folder 1168-1170)
  - Security Office, 1959-1963 (Box 132, Folder 1171)
  - Selective Service and veterans' affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 132, Folder 1172)
  - Senior pamphlets, information for, 1954-1960 (Box 132, Folder 1173)
  - Senior seminar in foreign policy, 1967-1969 (Box 132, Folder 1174)
  - Service Bureau, 1954-1969 (Box 132, Folder 1175-1176)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1953-1960 (Box 132, Folder 1177)
  - Seymour, President: memorial services, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 1178)
  - Sheffield Sterling Strathcona Hall, 1931-1932 (Box 133, Folder 1189A)
  - Sigma XI, 1962-1969 (Box 133, Folder 1190)
  - Silliman Report, 1954-1955 (Box 133, Folder 1190A)
  - Singer, Arthur Report, undated (Box 133, Folder 1191)
  - Skinner Collection, 1958-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1192)
  - Sociology Department, 1953-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1193)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, 1964-1969 (Box 133, Folder 1194)
  - Southerners at Yale, 1953 (Box 133, Folder 1194A)
  - Space allocation, 1965-1969 (Box 133, Folder 1195)
  - Speakers, 1951-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1196)
  - Stamp: Natural History Series, 1969-1970 (Box 133, Folder 1197)
  - Statistics, enrollment, 1966 (Box 133, Folder 1198)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, 1926 (Box 133, Folder 1198A)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps portrait: correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 134, Folder 1200)
  - Strike, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 1201-1202)
  - Student Appointment Bureau Scholarship, 1953-1958 (Box 134, Folder 1203)
  - Student correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1204)
  - Student Records Office, 1954-1969 (Box 134, Folder 1205)
  - Summer activities, 1963-1966 (Box 134, Folder 1206-1207)
  - Summer activities, 1965-1967 (Box 135, Folder 1208)
  - Summer Programs, 1967-1971 (Box 135, Folder 1209-1210)
  - Summer School bulletins, 1905-1907 (Box 135, Folder 1210A)
  - Summer sessions, 1958-1959 (Box 135, Folder 1211)
  - Surrey University, 1966 (Box 135, Folder 1212)
  - T-general
    - 1953-1956 (Box 135, Folder 1213)
    - 1959-1971 (Box 135, Folder 1214-1218)
  - Taft, Robert A. Memorial, 1962 (Box 135, Folder 1219)
  - Taft School, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 1221)
  - Teaching assistants, 1964-1969 (Box 136, Folder 1222)
  - Telephone usage forms, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 1223)
  - Town and Gown, 1959-1969 (Box 136, Folder 1224)
  - Transfers, accounts: forms, 1969 (Box 136, Folder 1225)
  - Transitional Year Program, Inc., 1969 (Box 136, Folder 1226)
  - Transistor Application Conference, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 1227)
  - Transportation Program, 1963 (Box 136, Folder 1228)
  - Travel expense reports, 1968-1971 (Box 136, Folder 1229)
  - Treasurer, candidates for, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 1230)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1953-1971 (Box 136, Folder 1231-1235)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1967-1968 (Box 137, Folder 1236)
  - Trumbull, John: two-hundredth anniversary of birth, 1955 (Box 137, Folder 1237)
  - Tuition, 1961-1962 (Box 137, Folder 1239)
  - Turner, Daniel, 1951 (Box 137, Folder 1240)
  - U-general, 1954-1971 (Box 137, Folder 1241)
  - Undergraduate Activities, 1953-1962 (Box 137, Folder 1242-1246)
  - Undergraduate affairs, 1959-1963 (Box 137, Folder 1247-1248)
  - Union, 1968-1969 (Box 137, Folder 1249)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1970 (Box 138, Folder 1250)
  - United Ministries in Higher Education, 1969-1971 (Box 138, Folder 1257)
  - Universities' admissions and financial aid policy, 138f1258, 1971 (Box 138, Folder 1258)
  - University Council, 1969-1970 (Box 138, Folder 1259)
  - Urban Studies, 1969 (Box 138, Folder 1260)
  - V-general, 1953-1971 (Box 139, Folder 1261-1263)
  - Vassar, 1966-1967 (Box 139, Folder 1264)
  - Visitors, 1959-1960 (Box 139, Folder 1265)
  - Visitors, booklet, 1959-1960 (Box 139, Folder 1266)
  - Visitors received by Secretary, 1963-1971 (Box 139, Folder 1267-1268)
  - Visits cancelled, 1961 (Box 139, Folder 1269)
  - W-general
    - 1953-1959 (Box 139, Folder 1270)
    - 1961-1968 (Box 139, Folder 1271-1272)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 140, Folder 1273-1275)
  - Wall Street Journal, Douglas Hallet article, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 1276)
  - Washington, George letter from Ezra Stiles to Washington (copy), 1781 (Box 140, Folder 1277)
  - Whiffenpoofs, 1959 (Box 140, Folder 1279)
  - Whiffenpoofs: information, undated (Box 140, Folder 1280)
  - Whitney, Payne Gymnasium and Ray Tomkins House (Box 140, Folder 1281)
    See: box 94, folder 773A
  - Wide World Lecture Bureau, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 1282)
  - Wiggin and Dana, 1956-1971 (Box 140, Folder 1283-1285)
  - Woodbridge Hall, 1902-1952 (Box 141, Folder 1286)
  - Wooden Spoon, 1926-1938 (Box 141, Folder 1287)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1957-1971 (Box 141, Folder 1288-1289)
  - Woolsey House, 1949 (Box 141, Folder 1290)
  - Women's College, 1939-1942 (Box 141, Folder 1291)
  - World War I: certificates, pamphlets, circulars, 1918 (Box 141, Folder 1292)
  - World War Memorials, 1920-1959 (Box 141, Folder 1293)
  - World War II: relatives of men on honor roll, 1956 (Box 141, Folder 1294)
  - Wright Hall, 1909-1912 (Box 141, Folder 1295)
  - W.Y.B.C., 1963-1964 (Box 141, Folder 1296)
  - X-Y-Z-general, 1961-1971 (Box 141, Folder 1297)
  - Y-general, 1959-1963 (Box 142, Folder 1298)
  - Yale Band, 1959-1963 (Box 142, Folder 1299)
  - Yale Club of Canada, 1959-1961 (Box 142, Folder 1300)
  - Yale Club of New Haven, 1953-1961 (Box 142, Folder 1301)
  - Yale Club of New York, 1953-1966 (Box 142, Folder 1302-1303)
  - Yale Club: recommendations, 1968-1970 (Box 142, Folder 1304-1306)
  - Yale Club of Washington and Government Program, 1958-1960 (Box 142, Folder 1307)
  - Yale Club of Washington and Government Program, 1961-1962 (Box 143, Folder 1308)
  - Yale Clubs and Associations, 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 1309)
  - Yale College, 1953-1971 (Box 143, Folder 1310-1315)
  - Yale Cooperative Corporation, 1968-1969 (Box 144, Folder 1316)
  - Yale Daily News, 1953-1971 (Box 144, Folder 1317-1322)
  - Yale, Elihu, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 1323)
  - Yale Film Festival, 1968 (Box 144, Folder 1324)
  - Yale Industrial Committee, 1965 (Box 144, Folder 1325)
  - Yale-in-China
    - 1962-1965 (Box 144, Folder 1326-1328)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 145, Folder 1329-1331)
  - Yale and Kiev exchange, 1961-1966 (Box 145, Folder 1332)
  - Yale Men Abroad Program, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 1333)
  - Yale name: copy of the act passed by the General Assembly of Connecticut authorizing name, 1887 (Box 145, Folder 1334)
  - Yale name: use of, 1962-1965 (Box 145, Folder 1335-1336)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital
    - 1964-1965 (Box 145, Folder 1337)
    - 1965-1969 (Box 146, Folder 1338-1343)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 147, Folder 1344-1345)
  - Yale Non-Faculty Action Committee, 1969 (Box 147, Folder 1346)
  - Yale Ph.D., one-hundredth anniversary, 1959-1961 (Box 147, Folder 1347)
  - Yale reports, 1964-1971 (Box 147, Folder 1348-1350)
  - Yale Review, 1962-1970 (Box 147, Folder 1351)
  - Yale Russian Seminar, 1962-1963 (Box 147, Folder 1352)
  - Yale Symphony, 1968-1971 (Box 148, Folder 1353)
  - Yale Travel Office, 1967-1971 (Box 148, Folder 1354)
  - Yale University News Bureau, 1953-1963 (Box 148, Folder 1355)
  - Yale University News Bureau, 1963-1971 (Box 148, Folder 1356-1360)
  - Yale University Press
    - 1954-1955 (Box 148, Folder 1361-1362)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 149, Folder 1363)
    - 1956-1969 (Box 149, Folder 1364)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 149, Folder 1365-1369)
    - 1962-1967 (Box 150, Folder 1370-1376)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 151, Folder 1377-1382)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 152, Folder 1383-1385)
    - Printing Office, 1957-1965 (Box 152, Folder 1386-1387)
  - Yale Volunteer Services, 1961-1963, 1965-1969 (Box 152, Folder 1388-1389)
  - Yale Women's Organization, 1964-1969 (Box 152, Folder 1390)
  - Yale Women's Organization, 1969-1971 (Box 153, Folder 1391)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1967-1971 (Box 153, Folder 1392-1393)
  - Zeta Psi Association, ETA Chapter, 1954-1971 (Box 153, Folder 1394-1396)
  - Zoology Department, 1959-1962 (Box 153, Folder 1397)
- University Secretary: Subject File, 1901-1972; Series III
  - Alumni Association George Young Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 154, Folder 1-7)
  - Alumni Day Programs, 1950-1964 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports: academic and research units
    - 1953-1954 (Box 155, Folder 9-13)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 156, Folder 14-18)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 157, Folder 19-22)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 158, Folder 23-26)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 159, Folder 27-29)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 160, Folder 30-34)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 35-39)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 162, Folder 40-45)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 163, Folder 46-51)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 164, Folder 52-59)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 60-66)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 166, Folder 67-76)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 167, Folder 77-84)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 168, Folder 85-92)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 93-97)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 98-102)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 103-108)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 172, Folder 109-115)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 172A, Folder 116-122)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 173, Folder 123-130)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 174, Folder 131-135)
  - Buildings
    - 1922-1937 (Box 175, Folder 136)
    - 1950-1957 (Box 175, Folder 137)
    - 1954-1960 (Box 175, Folder 138)
    - 1958-1964 (Box 175, Folder 139)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 175, Folder 140-142)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 175, Folder 143-145)
    - Hillhouse Avenue homes, undated (Box 175, Folder 146)
    - Original sheets for appendix, undated (Box 175, Folder 147)
  - Buildings: New, Dedication of
    - Art and Architecture: groundbreaking, 1961 (Box 176, Folder 148)
    - Art and Architecture, 1963 (Box 176, Folder 149-150)
    - Beinecke Library, 1963 (Box 176, Folder 151)
    - Computer Center, 1961 (Box 176, Folder 152)
    - Connecticut Hall, 1953-1957 (Box 176, Folder 153)
    - Dana Clinic, 1964 (Box 176, Folder 154)
    - Dana Operating Pavilion, 1961 (Box 176, Folder 155)
    - Divinity School dormitories, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 156)
    - Divinity School: opening service of 133rd year, 1954 (Box 176, Folder 157)
    - Dunham Electrical Engineering Annex, 1955-1958 (Box 176, Folder 158)
    - Dwight Chapel windows, 1961 (Box 176, Folder 159)
    - Edward S. Harkness Memorial Hall, 1953-1957 (Box 177, Folder 160)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health Laboratory, 1965 (Box 177, Folder 161)
    - Forestry School: 60th anniversary, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 162)
    - Gibbs Research Laboratories, 1955-1958 (Box 177, Folder 163)
    - Greeley Memorial Laboratory, 1959 (Box 177, Folder 164)
    - Helen Hadley Graduate Women's Dormitory, 1959 (Box 177, Folder 165)
    - Hunter Radiation Therapy Center, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 166)
    - Ingalls' Rink, 1957-1960 (Box 177, Folder 167)
    - Kline Chemistry Laboratory, 1965 (Box 177, Folder 168)
    - Kline Geology Laboratory, 1962-1963 (Box 178, Folder 169-170)
    - Korean War Memorial Tablets, 1959 (Box 178, Folder 171-172)
    - Linear Electron Accelerator, 1961-1962 (Box 178, Folder 173)
    - Mary S. Harkness Auditorium, 1960-1961 (Box 178, Folder 174)
    - Medical School Sesquicentennial, 1960-1961 (Box 178, Folder 175-177)
    - Memorial Apse, 1947 (Box 179, Folder 178)
    - Memorial tablets (Box 179, Folder 179)
    - Morse and Stiles Colleges: Lay of cornerstone, 1961 (Box 179, Folder 180)
    - Observatory, 1958 (Box 179, Folder 181)
    - Oceanography-Ornithology Wing, 1957-1959 (Box 179, Folder 182)
  - Buildings, Reservations for
    - 1953-1958 (Box 179, Folder 183)
    - 1961-1965 (Box 179, Folder 184-187)
  - Buildings, Use of
    - 1953-1957 (Box 180, Folder 188-190)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 180, Folder 191-193)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 180A, Folder 194-196)
  - Childs, Jane Coffin Memorial Fund
    - 1958-1960 (Box 181, Folder 197-201)
    - 1961 January-1962 March (Box 182, Folder 202-204)
    - 1962 June-1963 March (Box 182, Folder 205-207)
    - 1963 May-1963 December (Box 182, Folder 208-209)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 183, Folder 210-214)
    - 1967 April (Box 183, Folder 215)
    - 1967 June-July (Box 183, Folder 216)
    - 1967 October (Box 183, Folder 217)
    - 1967 October (Box 184, Folder 218)
    - 1968-1971 (Box 184, Folder 219-222)
  - Class of 1940, Reuben A. Holden, Class Secretary
    - 1938-1947 (Box 185, Folder 223)
    - 1940-1943 (Box 185, Folder 224)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 185, Folder 225-226)
    - 1946-1948 (Box 185, Folder 227)
    - 1946-1949 (Box 185, Folder 228-229)
    - 1947-1950 (Box 185, Folder 230-234)
    - 1950-1955 (Box 186, Folder 235-241)
    - 1955-1959 (Box 187, Folder 242-244)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 187, Folder 245-247)
    - 1964 (Box 187, Folder 248)
    - 1965-1970 (Box 188, Folder 249-257)
  - Commencement
    - 1946
      - Programs (Box 189, Folder 258)
      - Service for men lost in World War II (Box 189, Folder 259)
      - Convocation exercises (Box 189, Folder 260)
      - Engineering School graduation (Box 189, Folder 261-262)
    - 1950
      - Programs (Box 189, Folder 263-267)
    - 1951-1953
      - Programs (Box 190, Folder 268-270)
    - 1954
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 190, Folder 271)
      - Programs (Box 190, Folder 272)
      - Diplomas: correspondence and lists (Box 190, Folder 273-274)
    - 1955
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 191, Folder 275)
      - Programs (Box 191, Folder 276)
      - Diplomas: correspondence and lists (Box 191, Folder 277-278)
      - Platform (Box 191, Folder 279)
    - 1956
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 191, Folder 280-282)
      - Programs (Box 192, Folder 283)
      - Diplomas: correspondence and lists (Box 192, Folder 284-285)
      - Platform (Box 192, Folder 286)
    - 1957
      - Programs (Box 192, Folder 287)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 193, Folder 288)
      - Diplomas: correspondence and lists (Box 193, Folder 289)
      - Platform (Box 193, Folder 290)
      - Programs (Box 193, Folder 291-292)
      - Sample tickets, correspondence (Box 193, Folder 293)
      - Seating lists (Box 193, Folder 294)
    - 1958
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 194, Folder 295-299)
      - Diplomas (Box 194, Folder 300-301)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 195, Folder 302)
      - Programs (Box 195, Folder 303)
    - 1959
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 195, Folder 304-308)
      - Footnotes (Box 195, Folder 309)
      - Invitation list (Box 195, Folder 310-311)
      - Platform, Old Campus plans (Box 195, Folder 312)
      - Programs (Box 196, Folder 313-315)
      - Requisitions (Box 196, Folder 316)
      - Samples, correspondence (Box 196, Folder 317)
    - 1960
      - Banner bearers and marshals (Box 196, Folder 318)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 196, Folder 319-321)
      - Diplomas (Box 197, Folder 322-323)
      - Fellows to march (Box 197, Folder 324)
      - Programs (Box 197, Folder 325)
      - Requisitions (Box 197, Folder 326)
      - Special letters sent (Box 197, Folder 327)
    - 1961
      - Baccalaureate (Box 197, Folder 329)
      - Candidate for degree list (Box 197, Folder 330-332)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 198, Folder 333-336)
      - Honorary degrees (Box 198, Folder 337)
      - Honors (Box 198, Folder 338)
      - Programs (Box 198, Folder 339)
      - Program work copies (Box 198, Folder 340)
      - Seniors list (Box 198, Folder 341)
      - Student Marshalls (Box 198, Folder 342)
    - 1962
      - Baccalaureate (Box 199, Folder 343)
      - Citations, requisitions (Box 199, Folder 344)
      - Class Day (Box 199, Folder 345)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 199, Folder 346-348)
      - Faculty marshall material (Box 199, Folder 349)
      - Honorary degrees (Box 199, Folder 350)
      - Honorary degrees luncheon (Box 199, Folder 351)
      - Kennedy, J.F., President (Box 199, Folder 352)
      - News releases, press material (Box 199, Folder 353)
      - Programs (Box 199, Folder 354)
      - Rainy day procedure (Box 200, Folder 355)
      - Sample letters, tickets (Box 200, Folder 356)
      - Special luncheon, platform (Ingalls Rink and Old Campus) (Box 200, Folder 357)
      - Stage set-ups (Box 200, Folder 358)
      - Sterling Library detail (Box 200, Folder 359)
    - 1963
      - Baccalaureate (Box 200, Folder 361)
      - Citations (Box 200, Folder 362)
      - Class Day (Box 200, Folder 363)
      - Correspondence, memoranda (Box 200, Folder 364-366)